我們現在面臨能源危機  弗蘭克
We've got an energy crisis, Frank.
白宮應該...
Now what the White House needs to --
總統選擇對中國保持強硬態度
The president chose to remain tough on China.
不  那是被你逼的
No. You forced him to.
你選擇了馮  是你讓我和他見面的
You chose Feng. You're the one who put me in a room with him.
廚子手藝不好
The cook can't blame his ingredients
不能去怪原料差
if he doesn't like how they taste together.
如果釤的價格不降
If Samarium prices don't reduce,
市場只能隨之上調電價
the market will have no choice but to compensate.
那樣對每一個使用空調的人來說都是壞消息
That's bad for everyone who owns an air conditioner.
你應該去找總統本人談談
You should speak to the president himself.
總統最近不是很重視我的意見
the president hasn't placed much value on my advice lately.
我和你一樣  雷蒙德
I'm in the same boat as you, Raymond.
是啊
Yeah.
不同的是  你和他的辦公室只隔三道門
Difference being you've got an office three doors down from the Oval.
我們同心協力吧
Let's work together, for Christ sakes.
只要你願意  我可以忘記斯波特瑟爾維尼亞的事
I'm wiling to put Spotsylvania behind us if you are.
正合我意
I want nothing more.
那你會去跟他談
Then you'll talk to him?
我開會要遲到了  雷蒙德
Look, I'm late for a meeting, Raymond.
答應還是不答應  弗蘭克
Yes or no, Frank?
我不能保證他聽得進去
I can't guarantee he'll listen.
這不是答應
That's not a yes.
總比不答應強
But it's better than a no.
稱職的拳擊手都能看出對手什麼時候不行了
Any pugilist worth his salt knows when someone's on the ropes,
這時就該果斷連續向腹部出拳
that's when you throw a combination to the gut
左勾拳直擊下顎
and a left hook to the jaw.
翻譯  盧克·天意
翻譯  somehacker
翻譯  小飯
翻譯  衛老哥
翻譯  某豚
翻譯  肉鬆
翻譯  冬麟
翻譯  木月
時間軸  aaaBao
時間軸  吉吉
後期  餓得慌
特效  寶寶
顧問  老杜
校對  草草
總監  草草
紙牌屋
第二季  第六集
人人影視傾情奉獻
釤的價格他們絕不會讓步
Samarium is the last thing they'll let go of.
只要能源價格一直漲  他們就有談判籌碼
As long as our energy prices rise, they have the leverage.
如果我們只是靜觀其變呢  跟他們比瞪眼
Why don't we offer nothing? Move toward attrition.
如果中國不參加再融資債券拍賣
If China doesn't show at the refunding auction,
長期利率會一路飆升
long-term interest rates will spike.
一個星期後我們的十年期國債
And in a week yields on our 10-year notes
將突破7%大關
will pierce the seven-percent threshold.
那是有可能
That could happen.
但如果我們現在妥協  那就是必然了
But if we go soft now, that will happen.
你是說我們應該採取措施
You mean go on the offensive.
至少應該考慮一下
We should at least consider it.
中國人不吃敬酒  我們就上罰酒
The Chinese don't like carrots. Let's see how they like the stick.
怎麼做
Well, what might that look like?
增加糧食檢查的頻率
We could raise inspection rates on foodstuffs.
把他們的糧食扣在港口直到腐爛
Hold them in our ports till they rot.
提高多少
How much of a raise?
想要有效果要提高20%
20% if we want to draw blood.
用增加抽查次數的方式進行掩飾
Bury the move with increased spot checks all the way around.
這類措施不能解決眼前的問題
These sort of tactics don't solve the immediate problem.
人們現在交著三倍的電費
People are paying triple the standard rate for electric.
到八月份  就是五倍
We'll hit a five-fold increase by August.
如果您  總統先生  通過行政命令
What if you, Mr. President, by executive order,
從第三方手裏購買釤呢
purchase Samarium through a third party?
繞過中國
Cut the Chinese out.
迫使他們提高全球價格
Force them to either raise their prices worldwide
或是降低價格維持跟我們的交易
or lower them to keep direct flow with us.
當然  對外宣稱是為了國防需要進行釤儲備
We stockpile Samarium for denfense purposes, of course,
然後悄悄把多餘的釤賣給我們核能源方面的盟友
And quietly sell what we don't need to our friends in nuclear energy.
以優惠價格
At a discount.
核能源補助
A subsidy for nuclear power?
有錢人相互接濟  這別人會怎麼看啊
The richest of the rich? How's that gonna play?
我們正在面對國家危機
We're dealing with a national crisis.
我們不能受公眾輿論的影響
We can't get sidetracked with public opinion.
這能讓中國知道我們願意耐心等待
It would show China we're willing to wait this out.
我們有這份錢嗎
Do we have the resources?
我要計算一下
I'd have to run the numbers,
預期波動  考慮不同模式
anticipate fluctuations, consider different models --
估計一下
Your best guess.
有  可以進行中度儲備
We do. For a moderate stockpile.
那好  以國防部名義起草請求
All right. Draw up a request from the Defense Department.
-是  先生  -琳達  起草行政命令
- Yes, sir.  - Linda, draft the executive order.
凱茜  確保我們能找到一個第三方
And Cathy, make sure we have a third-party conduit
購買釤
to purchase the Samarium.
跟印度買吧
We'll go through India.
那巴基斯坦可要不高興了
Well, that won't fly well with Pakistan.
我會提前告知他們  只要及時告知他們
I'll alert them in advance. As long as they're in the loop,
就沒什麼問題  我們又不欠他們什麼
we'll be all right. Not that we owe them any favors.
那好  開始工作吧
All right. Let's get to work.
貝茜  還加上E條款下的三條罪名
Come on, Betsy. Three additional counts under Section E?
三條已經很少了  反映了對犯罪意圖的狹義解釋
Three is low. It reflects a narrow interpretation of criminal intent.
你的委託人入侵了數據中心
Your client broke into a data center.
你能提供什麼
What's the offer?
我不會認罪的
I'm not doing a plea.
讓我來處理這個
Let me handle this.
他們不想開庭審判
They don't want a trial.
我能在公開法庭上高聲提出的問題
The questions I'll be raising loud and clear in open court...
盧卡斯  別這樣
Lucas, please.
我們也有問題  古德溫先生
We have our own questions, Mr. Goodwin.
比如  你怎麼會有這些
For example, what were you doing with these?
這不是我拍的
I didn't take these.
是在你公寓發現的
They were in your apartment.
安德伍德拍的
Underwood took them.
你覺得陪審團能信嗎
Do you really expect a jury to believe that?
是他  他們有一腿
He did. They were having an affair --
他們只會如實看待這些證據
Or are they gonna see them for what they are?
你迷戀巴恩斯女士
Proof of our obsession with Ms. Barnes
還編出一套荒唐的陰謀論
and the ludicrous conspiracy you have concocted
來解釋她的死
to explain her death.
你們開什麼條件
Tell us what you're offering.
你委託人供認以下罪名  E條款下一條
Your client pleads to one count under Section E
闖入數據中心
for breaking into a data center,
欺詐一條  偷《先驅報》的密碼
one count for fraud, for stealing the password from the Herald.
第一項獲罪10年  第二項10年  同時計算
10 years under Section E. 10 years for fraud. Served concurrently.
服刑7年可假釋
Eligible for parole in seven.
我想單獨跟委託人談談
I'd like to speak to my client, alone.
請關掉錄像錄音設備
Cameras and recording equipment off, please.
我介紹總統  他來介紹你
I'll introduce the president, then he'll introduce you.
如果他去  就不能點名軍方
If he's there, we can't mention the military.
只能說全國皆有這種現象
Just the endemic problem nationwide.
當然  我理解
Of course. I understand.
好  那再過一遍講詞
Good. So we should go through these speeches
看還有沒有...
and make sure that there's nothing --
你好  安德伍德夫人
Hi, Mrs. Underwood.
你好  克裏斯蒂娜
Hello, Christina.
沃剋夫人  您找我
Mrs. Walker, you asked for me?
我們要確認一下總統能不能
We need to confirm whether the president's going
去新奧爾良
to make it to New Orleans.
是這週五吧
This Friday, correct?
是  但我知道他今早有內閣會議
Yes. But I know he had a cabinet meeting this morning,
所以我想
so I imagine...
我這就去和琳達溝通一下
I'll talk to Linda right away.
謝謝
Thanks.
我知道你希望加勒特去  可能源危機的事
I know you want Garrett there. But with this energy crisis...
不是那個
No. It's not that.
怎麼了
What?
我不該說的
I shouldn't say anything.
這下你非說不可了
Well, now you have to tell me.
我就是向來不太喜歡克裏斯蒂娜
I've just never been very fond of her. Christina.
為什麼
Why not?
彼得·羅素
Peter Russo.
我就是不太喜歡跟老闆上床的女人
I just have a thing about women who sleep with their bosses.
不過我相信他們是真心相愛
Anyway, I'm sure whatever they had was genuine.
也不關我事  只要她工作做得好
It's none of my business, 'cause if she's doing a good job,
其他也無所謂
that's all that matters, right?
加勒特還挺滿意
Garrett seems to think she is.
那我就不多嘴了
Then I should just keep my feelings to myself.
如果總統不能去
So if the president is not able to be there,
對咱們或許也是好事
that could be a silver lining for us.
不用給軍方留面子了
We won't have to hold back with the military.
電話監聽  視頻監控  預謀犯罪
Phone taps. Video surveillance. Premeditation.
長期動機  你沒希望的
Sustained intent. They've got you cold.
如果我認罪  就沒人知道真相了
If I plead out, that's it. No one hears the truth.
你不認罪的話  根本沒人會聽你的
If you don't plead, no one will hear you, period.
一直到你七八十歲
Not until you're in your 70s.
你和漢默施密特談了嗎
Have you talked to Hammerschmidt yet?
你沒資格談條件
You're in no position to make demands.
你說了又不算
It's not up to you.
你只會惹惱他們
All you'll do is piss them off.
聽我說
Look,
這個交易很好
we've got a good deal here.
考慮到你的行為  算很不錯了
A great deal, considering what you did.
趁他們沒改主意  趕緊接受
You should take it before their change their mind.
湯姆·漢默施密特
Tom Hammerschmidt.
我要跟他談  否則就上法庭
I talk to him, or we're going to trial.
請抬起胳膊
Raise your arms, please.
這裏有什麼物品
You have something here?
項鏈
My neck chain.
請掏出來
May I see it?
真的嗎  我還得解領帶
Really? I gotta take off my tie.
必須看一下  先生
I need to see it, sir.
虔誠的基督徒啊  雷米
You're a good Christian, Remy.
我母親的  是她虔誠
My mother's. She was the good Christian.
那你也是個好兒子
Well, then you're just the good son.
謝謝
Thank you, sir.
外面熱吧
Hot out there, huh?
35.5度  車裏顯示的
96, according to my car.
以前在加夫尼也這麼熱
We had heat like that back in Gaffney,
那會兒還沒有空調
but we didn't know what air conditioning was,
我們認為夏天就該這麼難熬
so we just accepted as fact that summer was meant to be miserable.
加不加水
Neat or with water?
只要水  不要酒
Just the water. You can hold the bourbon.
得找個解決辦法
We need to find a solution
好讓這個夏天美國人民不那麼難熬
so that this one isn't miserable for 300 million people.
我有辦法了
I already have found a solution.
得了吧  弗蘭克  釤補助嗎
Oh, please, Frank. A Samarium subsidy?
是你還是雷蒙德表示懷疑
Is that your skepticism or Raymond's?
我  估計他也是
Mine. Anticipating his.
你倆還沒談過
So you haven't spoken to him yet.
我想向他提出他會同意的條件
I want to offer him something he can agree to.
他沒什麼選擇
Well, he doesn't have much of a choice.
你為什麼要把他逼入絕境
Why are you cornering him?
我把價錢減半  這是在幫他啊
I'm cutting the rate by half. I'd call that liberating him.
你知道他可不這麼看
You know that's not how he'll see it.
這場貿易戰讓北京方面
This trade war is preventing the refinery
遲遲不批准精煉廠項目
from being approved in Beijing.
目前  他跟馮的合資項目不是最重要的
His co-venture with Feng is not our highest priority right now.
稀土精煉廠能一勞永逸地解決這場危機
A rare earth refinery solves this crisis permanently.
那是三年之後了  這個夏天還是難熬
Three years from now. Not this summer.
不止如此  實施核能補助他至多不賠不賺
It's not just that. With the subsidy he'll break even at best,
那叫做生意嗎
there's no point in doing business to hover between red and black.
雷蒙德的利益對我來說比他的合資項目更不重要
Raymond's profits are an even lower priority to me than his co-venture.
告訴我你的目的  弗蘭克
Tell me what you're up to, Frank.
你跟塔斯克叫勁又得不到什麼
There's nothing to gain by locking horn with Tusk.
問你的客戶去  是塔斯克在叫勁
Ask your client. It's Tusk who's locking the horns.
他不喜歡矛盾
He's not a man who likes conflict.
我也不喜歡
Neither am I.
那就提出要求吧  我知道你不在乎核能補助
Then make the ask. 'Cause I know you don't care about the subsidy.
你有更大的目標
This is about something bigger.
我是個虔誠的基督徒  雷米  跟你母親一樣
I'm a good Christian, Remy, like your mother.
如果我想要別的  我會如實說的
I would tell you the truth if I wanted more.
你這是在發出信號嗎
You trying to send a message?
也許吧
Perhaps.
那內容是什麼
Which is?
頑固比順從的代價更大
That stubbornness is far more costly than obedience.
謝謝你的水
Thanks for the water.
你站錯隊了  雷米
You're on the wrong side, Remy.
是啊  我們中肯定有一人站錯
Yeah, well, one of us sure is.
大黃蜂飛回家後
And when the bumblebee flew home,
發現它的朋友們都抱著大桶蜂蜜在等他
all his friends were waiting with buckets honey, right?
他的朋友有蠕蟲  老鼠
And he's got his worm friend and his mouse friend
蜘蛛和蝸牛
and his spider friend and his snail friend.
它們都有許多蜂蜜  他看上去開心多了  是嗎
And they all had tons of honey. And he looks happier now, right?
-是啊  -是嗎
- Yeah! - Yeah?
於是他們開心地嗡嗡叫了起來
And so they all buzzzzed with happiness.
因為和朋友們在一起  生活會甜蜜得多
Because life is sweet when you spend it with your friend.
對嗎
Right?
你們會振動翅膀發出嗡鳴聲嗎  扇動小翅膀吧
Can you all buzz your wings? Buzz your little wings.
-我覺得會發出顫動的聲音  就像  -就像
- I think it would make a fluttering noise, like... - like
我不知道
I don't know.
你的顫動呢
Your flutters?
外面太熱了  你不該拋球  弗蘭西斯
It's too hot out here for you to be doing this, Francis.
我一直在喝水
I'm keeping hydrated.
這距離滿足規定嗎
Is that even regulation?
只到一半
It's only half.
但我不想讓媒體看到我在大街上練習
But I don't want the press to see practicing on the street.
還記得你在格林維爾開球那次嗎
You remember when you threw out that first pitch in Greenville?
我還在想你什麼時候會提到那事呢
I was wondering how long it was gonna take you to bring that up.
那次還不是全國電視台直播呢
That wasn't even on national television.
祝你好運
Good luck.
謝謝
Thank you.
格林維爾發生了什麼
What happened in Greenville?
格林維爾驅動隊
The Greenville Drive.
紅襪隊的1A隊
Single A team for the Red Sox.
主場作戰  我站在投球區土墩上
It was a home game. I get on the mound.
你從土墩上拋球嗎
You threw from the mound?
我想投個好球
Well, I wanted to throw a real pitch.
沒拋好嗎
Didn't make it.
差得遠呢
Not even close.
一半嗎
Halfway?
球在我鬆手前滑了出去
Ball slipped out of my hand just before I released it.
直線拋上了天
Went straight up in the air.
掉下來砸在我頭上  全場爆發大笑
Hit me on top of the head. The whole stadium burst a gut laughing.
喜劇性投球
Comic relief pitcher.
真會說話  密查姆
That's very clever, Meechum.
別告訴克萊爾
Don't tell Claire.
我聽到了
I heard that.
你跟他們處得真好
You're really good with them.
他們作手指畫時  你看到羅比了嗎
Did you see Robbie when they were finger-painting?
他脫掉了褲子  把他自己塗成藍色
He pulled down his pants and started painting himself blue.
-沒看到  -真的
- No. - Yeah.
但願我都洗乾淨了
Hope I got it all off.
艾利克斯和達利爾不會在意的
I'm sure Alex and Daria don't care.
他們總是讓他光著身子四處跑
They let him run around naked all the time.
是啊  但不會像光屁股的藍精靈
Yeah, but probably not with his Smurf ass.
我們今晚吃什麼
What do we want to do for dinner tonight?
我還有一些吃剩的雞肉  或者我們可以叫披薩
I've got some leftover chicken. Or we could order pizza.
披薩  不做菜
Pizza. No dishes.
是啊
Yeah.
我真的很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
我完全忘了有個朋友今晚要來接我
I -- I totally forgot I've got a friend picking me up tonight.
我完全忘了
I -- I completely blanked.
-沒事  -我真的很抱歉
- That's fine. - I'm really sorry.
不必道歉  是你男朋友嗎
Don't sweat it. Is it, uh, your boyfriend?
不是  只是一個老朋友
No, no. Um, just an old friend.
我能見見他嗎
Can I meet him?
他有點害羞  我不知道他是否願意
he's kinda shy. I do-- I don't know if he'd be up for --
沒事  沒關係
Totally cool. Don't worry about it.
我們改天再一起吃晚飯
We'll just do dinner another night.
明天見
I'll see you tomorrow.
好  你知道去哪裏找我
Yeah. You know where I'll be.
多久了
How long?
幾個月了
Couple of months.
為什麼不告訴我
Why didn't you tell me?
我不能去教堂嗎
I can't go to church?
你跟任何人有接觸都可能暴露我們
Anywhere you interact with other people opens us up to risk.
那我就該整天悶在呼叫中心
Right. I'm just supposed to slave away at the fucking call center
或是待在公寓裏不出來嗎
and then lock myself in the apartment.
別這麼小題大做
Don't get dramatic.
我喜歡這些人
I like the fellowship.
好嗎  沒有什麼可擔心的
Okay? There -- there's nothing to worry about there.
如果誰林奇堡的親戚來訪就能毀了一切
All it takes is one person's cousin to visit from Lynchburg.
或許是你的高中同學
Someone you went to high school with
或許是曾跟你共度良宵的客戶
or some client that you spend the night with.
那些人才不會出現在這裏
Those guys would never end up here.
你怎麼知道
You don't know that.
我就是知道
Yeah. I do.
你不就跑來這裏了嗎
You ended up here, didn't you?
我不能這麼生活
I can't live like this.
什麼
What?
我不能這麼生活
I can't live like this.
不  你能  你是個堅強的姑娘
Yes, you can. You're a strong girl.
就這些  這就是全部了嗎
That's it? That's everything?
我知道  你以前就聽過了
I know. You've heard it before.
作為一個朋友  盧卡斯  而不是記者
As a friend, Lucas. Not as a reporter.
我會接著挖
Now I dig.
我去打電話  去跑腿
I make the phone calls. I do the legwork.
他們對你還好嗎
They treating you okay?
還行
It's fine.
我不是問那個
That's not what I asked.
他們非常想達成認罪協議
They're pushing the plea deal pretty hard.
你在認真考慮嗎
How seriously are you considering it?
我想看看文章的影響
I want to see how this article impacts things.
你的律師怎麼說
What does your lawyer say?
他覺得這是個壞主意  我應該認罪
He thinks that's a bad idea. That I should take the plea.
也許你應該聽他的
Maybe you should listen to him.
不  我要文章  我確定
No. I want the article. That I'm certain of.
好吧  那我得趕快開始了
All right. I better get to it then.
謝謝你
Thank you.
你要知道
You need to know,
我會像對待其他報道一樣對待這件事
I'm gonna treat this the way I would any other story.
報道事實  你也許不會喜歡我寫的東西
Whatever the facts bear. You might not like what I write.
我明白
I get that.
我會先讓你看  然後你再做決定
I'll let you read it first. Then you can decide.
我就是這意思
That's all I'm asking.
挺住
Hang in there.
能幫我擦掉嗎  求你了
Can you wipe this off? Please?
其他核供應商都贊同嗎
And the other nuclear providers are on board?
大部分  除了雷蒙德的公司
Most. Except Raymond's company.
還有幾個
Couple of others.
湖港核電站  狼泉集團
Lakeport Nuclear. Wolf Springs.
我無法證明  但我敢肯定他們是串通好的
Now, I can't prove it, but I am absolutely sure they're colluding.
雷蒙德想讓我丟臉
Raymond wants to embarrass me.
我提出方案  核能說客卻不肯合作
I offer a solution, nuclear lobby turns its back.
他有拒絕的權利  總統先生
He has the right to refuse, Mr. President.
但他沒法操縱能源市場
What he cannot do is manipulate the energy market.
你想對經銷方施壓
You want to put pressure on the distribution side.
不僅施壓  徹底禁止縱向合併
More than pressure. Ban vertical integration entirely.
我們沒有那個管制權力
We don't have that regulatory power.
我們給《緊急能源法案》加一條反壟斷協議
We add an antitrust agreement to the Emergency Energy Bill.
我們打破地區性供應和經銷壟斷
We break up the regional supply and distribution monopolies,
就像當年對貝爾系統那樣
like the Bell System.
1984年  司法部結束了貝爾公司對電話服務的壟斷  將一個大公司拆分為獨立小公司
那馬上就會引起官司
It'll be challenged immediately in the courts.
我們不需要協議通過  只是用來嚇唬人
We don't need it to pass. We just need to threaten it.
看他會不會屈服
See if he falls into line.
這事能不能低調辦妥  不鬧上新聞
Is there a way to do that without it making its way into the news?
我不希望世界上最有錢的有錢人都給我打電話
I don't want the world's wealthiest one percent on my phone sheet.
當然可以  先生
There is absolutely a way to do that, sir.
你們的酒來了
Here you go.
週二晚上就這麼熱鬧
Crowded for a Tuesday night.
我們把室溫保持在18度  而且免費
We keep it at 65 degrees. And it's free.
一杯伏特加蘇打水18塊也叫免費嗎
If you call 18 bucks for a vodka soda free.
那也比電力公司的賬單便宜
Still cheaper than a Pepco bill.
那要看你喝多少了
Depends on how many you have?
你想讓我們喝醉嗎
You trying to get us drunk?
你喝得越醉  給的小費越多
Drunker you are, bigger your tip.
我不用喝醉就會好好答謝優質服務
I don't have to be drunk to appreciate good service.
我去找零錢
I'll get your change.
不用了
No, you won't.
謝謝你
Thank you.
你真不要臉
You're shameless.
所以我是個好說客  乾杯
Makes me a good lobbyist. Cheers.
傑姬  舉動很大膽  但是沒用的
So, Jackie, bold move, but it won't work.
你知道我們可以輕鬆通過這項修正案
You know we can pass this amendment in a heartbeat.
也許  但沒有人會遵守
Maybe. But no one'll comply.
它會被推翻  最後竹籃打水一場空
It'll get overturned. Big fuss for nothing.
也許會被推翻  但依然會留下印記
It might get overturned. But it gets ink along the way.
以我對雷蒙德·塔斯克的瞭解
One thing I learned about Raymond Tusk
他才不在乎什麼公眾意見
is he doesn't two bird shits about public opinion.
他的股東們在乎
His stockholders do.
只要他一句話
They'd jump in a pit of snakes
他們就會跳進蛇窩  把自己點著
and light themselves on fire if he gave the word.
我只求你能轉達我們的意圖
All I'm asking if that you convey our intentions.
為什麼找我  弗蘭克打個電話還不容易
Why me? Frank could easily pick up the phone.
你還叫他弗蘭克呢
You still call him Frank?
不會當面叫  我也盡量避免見他
Not to his face, which I try to keep to a minimum.
你不覺得在白宮有個能說上話的人很好嗎
Don't you appreciate having an ear in the White House?
如果真是那樣還好了  但最近我淨聽他說了
I wouldn't, if I had an ear. But lately all I've got is a mouth.
是啊  他不是很善於傾聽  對吧
Yeah. He's not the best listener, is he?
你要是為他工作就知道了
Try working for him.
你曾在他手下幹過嗎
You were on his staff?
八年  新聞發言人  那時你還沒進國會
Eight years. Press secretary. Before you joined Congress.
這倒說明了很多問題
That explains a lot.
比如什麼
Like what?
比如很多
Like a lot.
我就當你是在羞辱我了
I'll take that as an insult.
沒錯
You should.
這就走嗎  這就撇下我嗎
That's it? You're abandoning me?
不  我去買下一輪
No. I'm buying the next round.
禮尚往來嘛
I can't accept gifts from lobbyists without reciprocating.
而且我是個好幫手
Plus, I'm a good wingman.
這樣你能多跟那個酒吧女侍接觸
This gets you more face time with the barmaid.
弗萊迪燒烤餐館
弗萊迪
你都做好了嗎
You already got 'em ready?
你的手下通知我你要來了
Your guys gave me the heads-up you were coming.
希望他們沒有太早吵醒你
Well, I hope that they didn't wake you earlier than usual.
操  這麼熱我哪能睡得著
Fuck, man. With this heat I ain't sleeping much anyway.
怎麼  家裏沒有空調嗎
What? No AC at home?
我有空調  只是不想付賬單
Oh, I got a unit. I just don't want to pay the damn bill.
總的來說  這裏的溫度還可以
It's not too bad in here, all things considered.
那是因為我們在陰涼處
That's 'cause we in the shade.
過兩小時  你要是去外面人行道上
When you get outside a couple hours from now on that pavement,
滾燙的地面能把你的雞巴烤熟
fry your damn dick off from three feet below.
燒烤架那邊一定很難熬
Must be bad over that grill.
我都覺不出區別了
I can't tell the difference no more.
但是我跟你說
I tell you what, though.
氣溫超過37度  這裏的情況就會變糟
Stuff goes down aroundhere when the mercury pop a hundred.
之前在家裏打老婆的男人會到街上來打
Man who beat his wife at home will beat her right out on the street.
把我們的獸性都暴露出來了
Brings out the animal in us.
可不是開玩笑
It ain't no joke.
以前我會被什麼驚醒  槍聲
What used to wake me up? Gunshots.
你知道現在是什麼嗎  人們操的聲音
Now you know what does? People fucking.
又是呻吟又是尖叫  像巷子裏的貓
Moaning and screaming like god damn cats in the alley.
俗話說得好  天熱一身汗
You know what they say: When you get hot and sweaty,
脫衣就開干
it make you ripe and ready.
我喝多了
I drank too much.
我們都喝多了
We both did.
昨晚的事沒發生
Last night didn't happen.
我知道
I know.
我出門之後  一切公事公辦
When I walk out that door, it's business as usual.
沒有特殊優待
No special treatment.
別擔心  你不需要申請禁制令
Don't worry. You won't need a restraining order.
我很驚訝  你沒去找那個女招待
I'm surprised you didn't go for the waitress.
你比她性感得多
You're much sexier.
得了吧
Yeah, okay.
她為小費工作  而你運作國會
She works for tips. You run Congress.
只有一半
Only half of it.
那也比她厲害得多
That's half more than she does.
那麼不是我的身體吸引你
So it's not my body.
那雙腿還是挺不錯的
Those legs don't hurt.
你真是滿口胡言
You're so full of shit.
好吧  是你的聲音
Okay. It's your voice.
我的聲音
My voice?
讓我欲罷不能
It does something to me.
把塔斯克的意思轉達給我
Let me know what Tusk has to say.
不談公事  你還沒出門呢
Business hasn't started. You haven't walked out that door yet.
看好了
Watch me.
公事:跟雷·塔談過了
雷米·丹頓
他說最高法庭上見
謝謝你  傑姬
Thank you, Jackie.
我們去白宮
We're going to the White House.
小約翰在移動
Little John on the move.
我們提高賭注  把聯邦能源管理委員會拉進來
We raise the bet. We get FERC involved.
調查嗎
An investigation?
我們不需要國會來調用能源委員會
We don't need Congress to activate the Regulatory Commission.
但是價格聽證  會耗費好幾個月
But a price-fixing review? That would take months.
再說一次  只是威脅  不是真的
Again, it's the threat. Not the actuality.
他會採用同樣的對策
He'll employ the same logic.
把這事拿到法庭上去
Draw it out. Fight back with appeals.
但如果聯邦能源管理委員會開始行動
But he'll have to divulge his accounting
他的賬目就會曝光
if FERC takes action.
沒有哪個生意人願意公開賬目
Now, no businessman wants to open up his books,
尤其是四百三十億的賬目
especially one with $43 billion.
這事開始失控了  弗蘭克
This is getting outta hand, Frank.
我們不應該跟雷蒙德對著干
We shouldn't be duking it out with Raymond.
也許我們該和他談談
Maybe we should talk to him.
這正是他想要的  讓自己回到圈裏來
That's exactly what he wants. To force himself back into the mix.
把他排除在外有什麼好處呢
What's to be gained by shutting him out?
給他個教訓  讓他知道
The simple lesson that you cannot strong-arm
他不能強迫美國總統
the president of the United States.
我們不能淪落到跟他鬥氣
We can't devolve to a pissing contest.
我要給雷蒙德打電話  邀他來華盛頓
I'm gonna call Raymond. Invite him to Washington.
除非您徹底投降  否則他不會接受
He won't accept anything but total surrender.
我這就打電話
I'm making the call.
別把自己逼到那個地步
Don't put yourself in that position.
我知道如何維護政府的尊嚴  謝謝你
I know how to maintain the integrity of my office. Thank you.
謝謝您  總統先生
Thank you, Mr. President.
只要跟總統待兩分鐘
Two minutes with the president,
塔斯克就能再獲青睞
and Tusk may be back in his good graces.
我要阻止他們再度聯手
I need to disrupt the nuptials and prevent a second marriage.
克裏斯蒂娜
Christina?
很高興見到你
Good to see you.
拜託  你看上去棒極了
Please. You look great.
謝謝你
Thank you.
最近怎麼樣
How are things?
很好  琳達讓我忙得腳不著地
Great. Linda works me to the bone,
但這就是我想要的
but that's what I signed up for.
據我所知  你幹得很不錯
Well, from what I've heard, you're doing a great job.
很高興能聽到這樣的評價
Oh, that's really nice to hear.
我想跟你談談特莉莎
Look, I wanted to talk to you about Tricia.
你肯定注意到她仍在適應自己的角色
I'm sure you've noticed that she's still sort of adjusting to her role.
你是說自信方面嗎
You mean her confidence?
我覺得你應該主動去找她談
I think it would be great if you reached out to her.
讓她知道如果有什麼需要你會幫助她
Just let her know that you're there if there's anything that she needs.
我其實跟她不熟  我們見過  但是我
I don't really know her that well. I mean, we've met, but I...
沒關係
That's okay.
或者就告訴她  你很喜歡為總統工作
Maybe just tell her that you enjoy working for the president
你願意盡你所能幫助她
and you're there to be of help to her in any way you can.
-你不覺得那樣有點唐突嗎  -沒有
- You don't think that's a little -- I don't know -- brash? - No.
我就這麼去找她
For me to just approach her like that?
不會的
No. Not at all.
華盛頓先驅報
前僱員佐伊·巴恩斯加入頭條網
杜蘭特或提名國務卿
羅素獲得黨鞭辦公室支持  競選州長
議員得到副總統支持
你已接通斯克斯基宅
You've reached the Skorsky residence.
請在嗶聲後留言
Leave a message after the beep.
又是湯姆·漢默施密特  還是要找簡寧
Tom Hammerschmidt again. Still trying to reach Janine.
還是重要的事  謝謝
Still important. Thank you.
這是誰
漢默施密特整天都在往我們新聞處打電話
Hammerschmidt's been calling our press office all day.
我跟你一樣不希望鬧出任何新聞
I don't want a story to come out any more than you do.
否則我們會損失一名重要線人
We lose a major asset if it does.
你能以安保理由讓他噤聲嗎
Can you squash it for security reasons?
一旦讓媒體知道就不行了  第一修正案什麼的
Not once it's been shared with the press. First Amendment crap.
牢房並沒能解決問題
Ward isn't making things any easier.
她想邀個大功
She wants a notch in her belt.
我們給她一個機會了
We're giving her one.
不是古德溫  她想要奧爾西
Not Goodwin. She wants Orsay.
六年的首要通緝犯
Most Wanted list for six years.
我來搞定漢默施密特
I'll handle Hammerschmidt.
你得確保古德溫認罪
You need to make sure Goodwin takes the plea.
35年刑期  不許假釋
If 35 with no parole doesn't scare the piss out of him,
絕對能嚇倒他
I don't know what will.
別去嚇唬他
Then don't try to scare him.
讓他徹底絕望
Remove hope from equation.
我努力控制這件事
I tried to keep this contained.
我沒預料到漢默施密特會出現
I didn't anticipate Hammerschmidt.
斯克斯基女士在跟他合作嗎
Is Ms. Skorsky cooperating with him?
他給她打過電話
He's called her.
我在聯調局的朋友說他們沒交談過
My guy at the bureau said they haven't actually spoken.
至少沒在電話裏交談過
At least not on the phone.
如果鬧上法庭
If this goes to court...
不會的  先生
That won't happen, sir.
要是他發表了文章就會
It will if he publishes.
我來找你是因為我無法控制漢默施密特
I'm bringing this to you because I can't control Hammerschmidt.
我不知道該怎麼做
I don't know what to do.
我們要發動正面進攻  然後守住陣線
We need to invite a full-frontal attack. Then hold the line.
你要跟他談談嗎
You want to speak to him?
面對面  只有我們倆
Face to face. Just the two of us.
我覺得那不是個好主意  先生
I don't think that's a good idea, sir.
你有更好的主意嗎
You have a better idea?
沒有  先生
No, sir.
我們無法避免戰爭  但我們可以選擇戰場
We can't avoid the battle, but we can choose the battlefield.
把會面安排在白宮
Set up a meeting at the White House.
擺架子嚇唬他
We'll intimidate him with formality.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
副總統先生
Mr. Vice President?
我知道你沒有耐心聽道歉
I know you don't have patience for apologies,
但我很抱歉讓你失望了
but I'm sorry if I've let you down in any way.
我們集中精神解決眼前問題吧
Let's concentrate on what's in front of us.
我安排好之後會告訴你的
I'll let you know when I have a time set up.
-越快越好  -是  先生
- Soon as possible. - Yes, sir.
這算是長篇報道的概述嗎
So this is a sort of outline to the larger piece?
問題都在下一頁
With questions on the next page.
我們現在是私下談話
We're off the record.
對  私下談話
Yes. Off the record.
湯姆  我知道你關心這個年輕人
Now, Tom, I know that you care about this young man,
我也尊重你的職業精神
and I respect you as a journalist.
但這些問題
But these questions?
你怎麼不直接問我
Why don't you just ask me
為什麼不再掐死別人的寵物了
when I stopped strangling people's pets.
先生  羅素議員的死
Sir, the death of Congressman Russo --
你是說我的朋友  彼得·羅素
You mean my friend, Peter Russo,
他的自殺讓兩個年幼的孩子失去了父親
whose suicide left two small children with no father.
不  我不會回答關於那事的問題
No, I will not answer questions about that.
你好  我知道  不  告訴她我待會兒回電
Yes? I'm aware of that. No. Tell her I'll call her right back.
給你兩分鐘  剛剛是杜蘭特國務卿
Two minutes. Secretary Durant.
我可以在外面等你給她回電
I can wait outside for you to call her back --
不  我們說完
No, let's finish.
那麼
Now,
如果你打算發表這些內容
if you decide to print any of this,
如果你真能找到願意發表的出版機構
assuming you find an outlet that's willing to,
那麼  確實會讓我頭疼一陣
then, yes, it might cause me a headache for a day.
但我不會做出回應
But I will not engage.
在我看來  報道只會更加突出
And I think it will only prove to highlight
古德溫先生的論斷多麼可笑  我同情他
how ridiculous Mr. Goodwin's claims are. I pity him.
真心的  我覺得他需要幫助
I truly do. I think he needs help.
我採訪過很多精神異常的人  他沒瘋
I've interviewed many mentally ill people. He's not one of them.
我建議你把自己的文章再好好讀讀
Well, I would suggest that you read your own article again.
他只是非常痛苦  這兩者是有區別的
He's distressed. There's a difference.
我理解  看到他入獄對你打擊一定很大
Look, I understand. It must be a terrible blow to see him in prison.
但湯姆
But, Tom...
瑞秋·波斯納確有其人
Rachel Posner exists.
我找不到她  但我已經證實她不是捏造的
I haven't been able to find her, but I've proven she's not a fantasy.
羅伊·科佩尼科也是  這些人確實存在
The same goes for Roy Kapeniak. These people were born.
他們有社保號碼  既往住址...
They have social security numbers, past addresses, past --
全美各地的每個人都是如此
And so does everyone from California to Maine.
我和他們都有共謀嗎
Have I conspired with all of them?
你得承認  酒駕問題確實有些解釋不清的細節
You have to admit there are some troubling details regarding the DUI.
要知道  人們也是這麼說51區的
You know, people say the same thing about Area 51.
有很多軍事及外星人傳聞的地區  美國政府對此既不肯定也不否認
你可以盡情想像
You can conjure up little gray men if you really want to.
你殺了彼得·羅素嗎
Did you kill Peter Russo?
湯姆  你這就是自找沒趣了
Tom, you're embarrassing yourself.
你殺了佐伊·巴恩斯嗎
Did you kill Zoe Barnes?
這些荒唐事根本不值得我浪費這麼多時間
I've given you more time than this nonsense deserves.
我必須得問
I have to ask these questions.
要我提問的話  我只問一句
Well, the only question I would ask is
這樣的報道對古德溫先生有利還是有害
does this sort of article hurt or help Mr. Goodwin?
你得做你認為對的事
You have to do what you think is -- is right.
但我希望你能理解
But I hope you can understand
我無法認真對待這些問題  有損我的身份
if I don't demean myself by taking any of it seriously.
感謝您抽出時間  副總統先生
I appreciate your time, Mr. Vice President.
怎麼樣
How did it go?
我的任務完成了  把這事了結了吧  道格
I did my part. Now put it to bed, Doug.
我不會允許自己再面對這樣的處境
I won't submit myself to this sort of exposure again.
是  先生
Yes, sir.
塔斯克和總統見面了嗎
Has Tusk met with the president yet?
琳達說他們約了四點半
Linda said they're meeting at 4:30.
聯繫雷米  確保他上飛機前我能見他一面
Call Remy. Make sure he doesn't get on his plane before I see him.
這就去辦
I'm on it.
沃剋夫人
Oh, Mrs. Walker?
我只想說  我非常榮幸
I just wanted to say how rewarding it's been,
能在白宮西樓工作
working here in the West Wing.
為您丈夫工作  我很自豪
And I'm so proud to be working for your husband.
謝謝  我知道他賞識你的勤奮
Thank you. I know he appreciates all your hard work.
既然我現在在他身邊工作
Well, now that I'm working so closely with him,
如果有什麼我能幫到您的
if there's anything I can do for you,
任何能幫您或他減輕負擔的事...
anything that would make yours or his life easier...
繼續做好你的工作就行
Just keep doing what you're doing.
我是真心的  您別客氣
Truly, anything.
我想讓您知道  你們可以依靠我
I want you to know you can rely on me. Both of you.
我知道  謝謝  克裏斯蒂娜
I know that. Thank you, Christina.
謝謝  沃剋夫人
Thanks, Mrs. Walker.
-讓我來  -沒事  我手不太聽使喚
- Oh, here. Let me. - Oh, it's just my hands.
-很難受嗎  -是啊  今晚估計要下雨
- Are they bothering you? - Yeah. Probably gonna get rain tonight.
我去開門
I'll get it.
不用  繼續攪拌肉湯就行
Um, no. Just, uh, keep the broth moving.
我是聯調局的格林特工
Agent Green, FBI.
有空嗎  斯克斯基女士
Do you have a moment, Ms. Skorsky?
有  我...
Yeah. I...
我們能進去嗎
May we come in?
我得把爐子關了
I just need to turn the stove off.
-待在這兒  媽媽  -是誰
- Stay in here, Mom. - Who is it?
待在這兒就是了
Just stay in here.
只有那一次嗎
Only that once?
之後我就沒見過他了  也沒回他電話
And I haven't seen him since, or returned his calls.
他幾次試圖聯繫你
How many times has he tried to call you?
我不知道  大概八九次吧
I don't know. Eight or nine times, maybe.
之後他消停了一段時間
And then he stopped after a while.
他提到過機器人希羅尼穆斯或嘉文·奧爾西嗎
Did he mention anything about Hieronymus Bot or Gavin Orsay?
我覺得我該找個律師來
You know, I think I should talk to a lawyer.
現在我們並不懷疑你是同謀
Right now you're not suspected of being an accomplice.
如果你找律師  那我們就要考慮一下了
If you call a lawyer, we might have to reconsider.
-他提到了個黑客  -希羅尼穆斯
- He mentioned some hacker. - Hieronymus.
我告訴他  聯繫那個人不是什麼好主意
I told him I thought it was a bad idea to contact him.
你知道他的說法嗎
Are you aware of what he's claiming?
不
No.
他說你在跟他合作
That you and he were working together.
你也相信他那套陰謀論
That you believe in this conspiracy theory.
是你收到了巴恩斯女士的私密照片
That it was you who received explicit photos of Ms. Barnes.
這些都是真的嗎
Is any of that true?
你得跟我們回華盛頓
We need you to come back to D.C. with us
在聯邦檢察官的見證下簽署這份聲明
and sign this statement in the presence of the U.S. attorney.
-你們想讓我指證他說謊嗎  -他沒有嗎
- You want me to call him a liar. - Isn't he?
我不能這樣對他
I can't do that to him.
你還得和湯姆·漢默施密特談談
We also need you to speak with Tom Hammerschmidt.
求求你們  能別把我扯進來嗎
You know what? Please, can you just keep me out of this?
我和那個黑客毫無瓜葛...
I had nothing to do with the hacker or the...
斯克斯基女士  我們願意相信你
Ms. Skorsky, we want to believe you,
你寫下來我們就相信你
and we will if you put all of it in writing.
他沒犯罪  你們查錯人了
He's not a criminal. You're going after the wrong person.
如果你們認為你們能嚇唬我
And if you think that you can intimidate me,
在我自己家這樣騷擾我
harass me like this in my own home,
我會提出正式投訴
I will file a formal complaint.
你語氣越來越像他了
You're starting to sound an awful lot like him.
你們不能逮捕我  我什麼都沒做
You can't arrest me. I haven't done anything.
你們快走
I'd like you to leave.
我有權請律師  而且你們沒有逮捕令
I have a right to legal counsel, and you haven't presented a warrant.
我們可以逮捕你  斯克斯基女士
We can arrest you, Ms. Skorsky,
以教唆網絡恐怖主義的罪名
for abetting an act of cyber terrorism.
如果你接下來三年都耗在法庭上
Who's going to take care of your mother while you're
誰來照顧你母親呢
spending the next three years in courtrooms?
麻煩您抬手
Would you please raise your arms?
-密查姆  不用了  -先生
- No, Meechum. - Sir...
密查姆  我知道你不想跟我握手
Meechum. I know you don't want to shake my hand,
我們就直接略過吧
so we'll just skip that part.
總統完全沒有提
The president didn't mention anything about it.
他為什麼要提  抓你個冷不丁更好
Why would he? The better to catch you off-guard.
那你為什麼要提
Then why would you?
好避免不必要的衝突
So we can avoid unnecessary conflict.
加勒特可不會撒謊
Garrett's not a good liar.
真正會說謊的人總是讓人覺得
The gift of a good liar is making people think
他天生不會說謊
you lack a talent for lying.
我遠比你瞭解他
I know him far better than you
我知道他天生會什麼  不會什麼
and so I know what talents he has and lacks.
但假設他確實說謊了
But let's assume he did lie.
我不擔心聯邦能源管理委員會的調查
I'm not intimidated by a FERC investigation.
聽證會還沒開始
You'd have grid overload and brown-outs
就會出現電網過載  燈火管制
before you could even get a hearing.
你在蓄意抬高電價
You are deliberately keeping electric prices at inflated rates,
這是違法的
which is illegal.
不  這是對自由市場的反應
No. I'm responding to free market.
是受監管的自由市場
A regulated free market.
你為什麼這麼做  弗蘭克
Why are you doing this, Frank?
雷米也這樣問過我
Remy asked me the same thing.
你這是故意找我茬
You're making this about me.
不是針對你  雷蒙德
This isn't personal, Raymond.
能源市場的健全是我唯一的考慮
The integrity of our energy markets is my only concern.
你當然是針對我
Of course it's personal.
我讓你說服加勒特不再與中國針鋒相對
I asked you personally to convince Garrett to pull back from China.
而你偏偏跟我對著干
You personally chose not to.
你還故意破壞峰會
You personally sabotaged the summit.
-我政治生涯中從未  -你還故意操縱內閣
- I have never once in my political career allow - And you personally advised the cabinet
-因私人感情而耽誤正事  -把我逼上絕路
- personal feelings to get in the way of pragmatic... - to push me up against the wall.
別跟我耍花招  弗蘭克  我耍不動了
Do not try and spin me, Frank. I am too old to tango.
那我就直說了
Then I'll be blunt.
接受核能補助  否則就面對能源委員會
Accept the subsidies or deal with FERC.
沒有第三條路可選
There is no third way here.
你是故意想毀掉總統嗎
Are you intentionally trying to destroy the president?
我是想保護總統  免受你的傷害
I'm trying to protect the president. From you.
你是在為國務卿提名的事報復我吧
This is about the secretary of state nomination, isn't it?
我現在是副總統了  雷蒙德
I'm the vice president now, Raymond.
我不會為陳年往事掉淚
I don't cry over what happened in kindergarten.
我力保你  你才當上副總統
You're vice president because I vouched for you.
因為你別無選擇
Because you had no other options.
這是政治需要
Political necessity.
給你24小時做決定
You have 24 hours to decide.
不用送了
I'll show myself out.
你好
Hello.
雷蒙德  這是克萊爾
Raymond, this is Claire.
安德伍德夫人  見到你很榮幸
Mrs. Underwood, it is an honor.
我妻子珍  很欣賞你最近做出的種種努力
Jean-- my wife-- has been very taken with your recent efforts.
改天我一定要見見她
Well, I'd like to meet her one day.
我相信她肯定非常願意
She would very much like that, I'm sure.
那你怎麼看呢
And what about you?
什麼意思
I'm sorry?
我們最近在做的事  你怎麼看呢
What are your thoughts about our recent efforts?
防止不必要的暴力  我當然支持
Oh. I am in favor of anything that prevents unnecessary violence.
很高興見到你  安德伍德夫人
It's nice to meet you, Mrs. Underwood.
祝你今晚開球好運  副總統先生
And, good luck with that first pitch tonight, Mr. Vice President.
這次要投進本壘板  夫人再見
Make it to the plate this time. Ma'am.
這防彈背心真不舒服
This Kevlar is cooking me.
必須得穿  先生
We have to use it, sir.
我練習時沒穿過  這下胳膊都轉不動了
Well, I didn't practice with it, and now I can hardly rotate my arm.
我該提醒您的  對不起
I should have mentioned it. I apologize.
這球要是過不了本壘板  我拿你是問
If this ball doesn't make it over the plate, it's your ass.
你在這兒幹什麼  沒事可做嗎
And what are you doing here? Don't you have things to do?
我沒來過卡姆登球場
Never been to Camden Yards.
女士們先生們  馬上將投出今晚第一球
Ladies and gentlemen, here to throw out the first pitch tonight,
我們有幸請上  美國副總統
we are honored to introduce the vice president of the United States,
弗蘭克·安德伍德
Frank Underwood.
先生  密查姆的球
Boss, boss. Meechum's ball.
非常感謝  吉祥物呢
Thank you very much. Where's the mascot?
唱得真好
Beautifully done.
晚上好
Good evening.
今晚很熱  大家都想趕快看比賽
Now I know it's a hot night and you all want to get to the baseball.
所以我一投出這玩意兒
So as soon as I throw this sucker,
大家就喝點東西  享受比賽
grab a drink, enjoy the game,
祝兩隊好運
and best of luck to both teams.
我收回那句話  這是在卡姆登球場啊
Scratch that. We're at Camden Yards.
金鶯隊加油
Go Orioles!
快走  快走
Go, go!
據說是控制節點的
I'm told the distribution line that controls
配電線路造成了供電中斷
the pinch point caused the outages.
貝科  你的一家公司
BAPCO. One of your companies.
是的  電量出問題了
Yes, sir. There was a capacity issue.
我的人在以最快速度搶修
We're working as quickly as we can to resolve it.
有三位州長給我打過電話了
Well, I've got three governors calling.
醫院在用應急電源  你們最好盡快修理
Hospitals on emergency power. So quickly better mean quickly.
最快也要2到3個小時  也許能快些
The latest estimate I got was two to three hours, maybe sooner.
雷蒙德  這是故意的嗎
Raymond, was this intentional?
先生  我知道你最近不怎待見我
Sir, I know you don't hold me in the highest regard at the moment.
但是你居然會這麼想  我很吃驚
But I am alarmed that you could even entertain such a thought.
但這時候出現這種事讓人很難相信是巧合
Yeah, well, the timing makes coincidence hard to swallow.
是熱浪的緣故  熱浪會讓電網達到使用極限
There is a heat wave. That always pushes the grid to its limits.
好吧  盡快讓人們擺脫黑暗
All right, let's get the people out of the dark.
每30分鐘報告一次進展情況
Updates every 30 minutes on your progress.
先生  我要通知你  我明天可能要
I should inform you, sir, that I may need to take
關閉兩座電廠做不定期維修
two of my plants offline tomorrow for unscheduled maintenance.
什麼  哪兩座廠
Why? Which ones?
佐治亞州和田納西州
Georgia and Tennessee.
這次停電使這兩座廠的負荷很大
This blackout has put a great deal of stress on them.
我的工程師們擔心燃料棒密封條破損
My engineers are concerned about the seals on the fuel rods.
那麼東南部也要斷電嗎
So we're looking at outages on the southeast grid, too?
有可能  幾天吧
Could be. For a few days.
這絕對不行
No, that's unacceptable.
安全第一   我們不希望出事故
Safety comes first. We don't want an accident.
好吧  詳細情況報告給琳達  盡快
All right, let's get a full report to Linda, ASAP.
是  先生  謝謝你
Yes, sir. Thank you, sir.
他在耍花招
He's toying with you.
不  或許真有這樣的安全問題
No, this could be a legitimate safety issue.
他想奪回權力  那幾個電廠沒事
He wants a seat back at the table. Those plants are fine.
他為什麼這麼做  我們的確有分歧
Why is he doing this? We've had our differences,
但非要做出這麼偏激的事嗎
but something drastic like this?
我跟他說了能源委員會可能會展開聽證會
Well, I did tell him about the possible FERC action.
什麼
You did what?
他打電話給我  我接了電話
Well, he called me. I answered the call.
你怎麼不立即通知我
Why didn't you inform me immediately?
他說你們的談話很有成效
He told me you had a productive talk.
他同意核能補助的事  我以為你們談妥了
That he was on board with the subsidy. I assumed everything was fine.
他提議進行新一輪貿易談判
He was proposing renewed trade talks.
我們根本沒談核能補助的事
We didn't talk about the subsidy at all.
他把我們倆都給耍了
He's playing both of us then.
如果他說他同意了
If he told you he was on board,
你為什麼還提能源委員會的事呢
why'd you bring up FERC?
我說這下我放心了
I told him I was relieved.
要是他不答應  我們可要採取行動了
That we could have taken action if he didn't comply.
你覺得他是在套你的話嗎
You think he's fishing?
想套出我們下一步行動
To see what our next move might be?
就是這樣  先生
I think so, sir. I mean,
南部兩個發電廠的事他在說謊
he is lying about those two plants in the south.
我們不能猜測  一定要確定
Well, we can't guess. We have to be certain.
您想讓雷蒙德·塔斯克來做風險評估
Well, do you want Raymond Tusk to assess that risk?
還是政府來做
Or the United States government?
你是說我們接管他的電廠嗎
Are you suggesting we take over his facilities?
有過這樣的先例
There is precedent there.
伍德羅·威爾遜接管鐵路三年整
Woodrow Wilson did it with the railroads for three full years.
那是戰爭時期
In a time of war.
是在危急時期  就像現在這樣
In a time of emergency, which is what this is.
人民需要一位領袖  總統先生
The country needs a leader, Mr. President.
滿足他們  別向雷蒙德·塔斯克屈服
Give them one. Do not bend to Raymond Tusk.
看完了
I'm done.
我說過你可能不喜歡
I said you might not like it.
這讓我看起來像是瘋了
It makes me seem crazy.
這是最收斂的版本了
This is the most toned-down version.
我盡力用最和善的口吻  不摻入偏見
I tried to be as kind as I could without being biased.
你不希望這報道公諸於眾吧
I don't think you want this going out into the world.
我能和簡寧談談嗎
Can I talk to Janine?
讓他走
Tell him to go.
他想讓你離開
He wants you to leave.
-你說了謊  -盧卡斯
- You lied. - Lucas...
你騙了湯姆  也騙了聯邦檢察官
You lied to Tom. You lied to the U.S. Attorney.
-我不知道還能怎麼辦  -說真話
- I didn't know what else to do. - Tell the truth.
他們會逮捕我  他們會讓我失去信譽
They'll arrest me. They'll discredit everything I say.
到時  人們會像不相信你那樣不相信我
And nobody is going to believe me more than they believe you.
但我們能讓公眾知道  讓人們產生疑問
But we can get the story out there. Get people asking questions.
不  他們只會覺得我們倆都瘋了
No. It'll just look like two crazy people instead of one.
所以你打算自保
So you're saving yourself.
我想保護我們兩個人
I'm trying to save the both of us.
拜託了
Please.
認罪吧
Take the plea.
-我是無罪的  -你不是
- I'm not guilty. - You are.
你犯了罪
You committed a crime.
-罪名還不止一項  -但不包括謀殺
- Multiple crimes. - Not murder.
承認罪行  好好表現  早點出來
Take the plea. Be good. Get out early.
所有人都坑我
Everybody -- everybody's fucked me.
如果我是想害你  就不會來了
If I was trying to fuck you I wouldn't be here.
他要逃脫罪責了  是嗎
He's gonna get away with it, isn't he?
是的
Yes, he is.
-有加冰的茶嗎  給我一杯  -沒有
- Take an iced tea if you have any. - We don't.
我真不想總這樣偷偷摸摸的
I wish I didn't have to keep coming through back doors like this.
這不是不想讓新聞界的朋友
Well, we wouldn't want our friends in the fourth estate
知道你來這裏嘛
to know you were here, would we?
特別是你費了好大的功夫
Especially since you've gone to such lengths
一直置身政治鬥爭之外
to remain above the fray of politics.
你不能奪走發電廠  弗蘭克
You can't seize the plants, Frank.
我們還沒得手呢
We haven't seized anything yet.
我們有這準備  但只要你合作就不會那樣
We're ready to, but we won't if you cooperate.
這是違法的
It's illegal.
並不違法  你心裏清楚
It's not. You know that.
緊急情況下  總統可以下達行政命令
The president can issue an executive order in times of emergency.
我會在法庭上據理力爭
I'll fight it in court.
那比能源委員會的調查更費時
Which will take even longer than a FERC investigation would.
而在此期間  你的發電廠無法盈利
And in the meantime, you make nothing from those plants.
我們說好的
We agreed.
就在這裏  我們達成了協議
Right here in this room, we agreed to work together.
做出了合作的承諾
We agreed as men of our word.
我一直信守承諾
And I held up my end of that bargain
-可你在法案的事上背信棄義  -我讓雷米去協助你了
- until you abandoned me on the bill. - I sent Remy to help you.
那是法案通過參議院之後  你之前可沒幫忙
After I got it passed through the Senate with no help from you.
我不能和總統鬧僵
I had to protect my relationship with the president.
斯波特瑟爾韋尼亞峰會期間你還企圖利用我
And then you tried to use me during the summit in Spotsylvania.
我活著不是為了做你最好的朋友
I was not put on this earth to be your best friend
也不是為了和你分享我的所有情報
or to share every piece of information I have with you.
我們只是達成了互利共贏的合作關係
We agreed to a mutually beneficial partnership. That's all.
是的  而我現在發現
Yes. And what's become very clear to me
跟你合作對我沒有任何好處
is that I benefit in no way from this partnership.
我們就不裝傻了
Let's not pretend to be naive.
我們最看重的都是個人利益
We both respect self-interest above all else.
現在  雙方利益不再一致
Our versions of that no longer align.
你就要犯下無法挽回的錯誤了
You are on the verge of making an irreversible mistake,
副總統先生
Mr. Vice President.
我的確可能是在犯錯  誰知道呢
I may well be making a mistake. Who knows?
我只知道你會聯繫琳達
What I do know is that you'll be calling Linda
告訴她你接受核能補助
and telling her that you'll accept the subsidies.
你有錢  雷蒙德
You may have all the money, Raymond,
但我有權
but I have all the men with guns.
這是設好號碼的一次性電話  她在等你答覆
It's a burner, pre-dialed. She's expecting.
對了  這是昨晚的
Oh, and, uh, yes. From last night.
按行話說  現在輪到你發球了
The ball's in your court, as they say.
上帝  你嚇死我了
Oh, Jesus Christ. You scared the shit outta me.
你就這麼隨隨便便地喊上帝嗎
Are you supposed to take the lord's name in vain like that?
繼續開著
Leave it on.
電費太貴
It costs too much.
我會付的
I'll take care of it.
古德溫認罪了  他要進監獄了
Goodwin took the plea. He's going away.
所以一切都結束了嗎
So does that mean this is all over?
沒有  我們還是要小心
No. We still have to be careful.
為什麼  沒有他  就不會有人找我了吧
But why? If he's gone, then nobody's looking for me, right?
據我們所知沒有
Not that we know of.
在確保萬無一失之前  一切照常
Until we know, nothing changes.
那你來就是為了讓我空歡喜一場嗎
So what, you just came over here to get my hopes up?
我來是為了確保你今晚不去教堂
I came here to make sure that you don't go to church tonight.
你想幹我嗎
Do you want to fuck me?
-這才是你的本意吧  -不是
- Is that what this is all about? - No.
你以前幹過我
You've done it before.
那不一樣
That was different.
夠了
Stop it.
我一向能察覺男人對我的慾望
If there's one thing I know, it's when a man wants me.
我在教會得知了拉結的故事
I learned who Rachel was in church.
拉結是《聖經》中和瑞秋同名的女子
她年輕漂亮
She was young and beautiful.
雅各在她照看羊喝水時愛上了她
Jacob fell in love with her while she was watering a lamb.
他做了七年的工
And she became his wife after he worked seven years
才終於娶到她
to earn her hand in marriage.
拉結有個叫約瑟的兒子
Rachel had one son. Joseph.
後來他成了國王
He became a king.
你餓不餓
Are you hungry?
這一集中  能源大亨塔斯克用"拉閘限電"的手段來要挾總統
現實中美國的能源巨頭可不敢如此囂張
現實中美國聯邦政府對能源公司的監管是相當嚴格的
能源部對企業的日常運營有諸多法規限制
一旦出現事故  造成污染
公司會受司法部的調查  起訴  承擔嚴重後果
2010年4月  英國石油公司鑽井平台發生事故
造成墨西哥灣嚴重污染  美國司法部的調查至今仍未結束
除了多名直接責任人被起訴
英國石油公司截止目前已經在多宗訴訟中賠償了422億美元
美國作為世界上最大的能源消耗國  如何解決長期的能源供應
同時兼顧環境保護  一直是兩黨的爭論焦點
共和黨在能源問題上主張充分利用美國的石油資源
放鬆對傳統能源行業的監管
民主黨則推崇綠色可再生能源
同時通過立法監管對石油和煤炭企業嚴加限制
過去幾年中  由於美國發現了大量的頁岩氣儲備
同時開採技術有了新的突破  渴望在2020年實現"北美能源獨立"
不再依靠北美以外地區的能源進口
所以在頁岩氣價格迅速下降的背景下
奧巴馬政府主張在能源上採取"百花齊放"的政策
在推動新型能源的同時  也鼓勵傳統能源的發展
但是由於民主黨左派一味強調環境和氣候變化問題
美國傳統能源行業普遍認為現政府的政策極大地束縛了行業的發展
由於兩黨在能源問題上立場相左
所以現實中的塔斯克這樣的能源巨頭非常注意本行業的公共形象
如果有"拉閘限電"這樣的事情發生  不僅涉及的公司會被調查
在民怨沸騰的情況下  國會也極可能迅速介入
通過立法手段對整個行業加強監管